Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod. My name is Marco.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。我是Marco。
My name is Catherine and we're talking about the stars today.
我是Catherine，今天我们聊的是关于星星的话题。
That's right. Today we're going to talk about a very popular subject. Many people believe
没错。今天我们要讨论一个非常受欢迎的话题。很多人相信
in the horoscope.
星座运势。
So a horoscope is basically a system, a very old system of determining your future and
所以星座运势基本上是一种系统，一种非常古老的系统，用来预测你的未来和
describing your personality. And so it all depends on when you were born and where you
描述你的性格。这一切都取决于你出生时的日期和
were born. So what stars were in the sky when you were born.
地点。也就是你出生时天空中的星星是什么。
That's right. So basically, as many of you may know, there are 12 signs and we're going
没错。所以基本上，正如你们很多人可能知道的，有12个星座，我们会
to talk about a couple of them and a little bit more about horoscopes and this, I don't
聊其中几个，以及更多关于星座运势的内容，这个，我不知道，我觉得它有点像科学的一个分支或者……
know, I guess it's kind of like a branch of science or...
伪科学。
Pseudo-science.
Yeah, I don't think there's much testing that's going on, but it's definitely something that
是啊，我觉得没多少测试在进行，但它绝对是
a lot of people believe in. So let's take a listen to today's dialogue and we'll be
很多人相信的东西。那么让我们听一下今天的对话，我们一会儿
back in a moment to talk more about it.
回来再聊更多。
Hey, Lydia, what are you reading?
嘿，Lydia，你在看什么？
I'm looking at my horoscope for this month. My outlook is very positive. It says that
我在看这个月的星座运势。我的前景非常乐观。上面说
I should take a vacation to someplace exotic and that I will have a passionate summer fling.
我应该去一个异国风情的地方度假，还会有一段充满激情的夏日恋情。
What are you talking about? Let me see that. What are horoscopes?
你在说什么？让我看看。星座运势是什么？
It's a prediction of your month based on your zodiac sign. You have a different sign for
它是根据你的星座对你这个月的预测。你有不同的星座，对应
the month and date you were born in. I was born on April 15th, so I'm an Aries. When
你出生的月份和日期。我出生在4月15日，所以我是白羊座。你
were you born?
是什么时候出生的？
January 5th.
1月5日。
Let's see. You're a Capricorn. It says that you'll be feeling stress at work, but you
让我看看。你是摩羯座。上面说你会在工作中感到压力，但
could see new exciting developments in your love life. Looks like we'll both have interesting
你的爱情生活可能会有令人兴奋的新发展。看来我们俩都会有一个有趣的
summers.
夏天。
That's bogus. I don't feel any stress at work and my love life is practically non-existent.
那都是胡扯。我在工作中一点压力都没有，我的爱情生活也几乎不存在。
This zodiac stuff is all a bunch of nonsense.
这些星座的东西全是胡说八道。
No it's not. Your astrology sign can tell you a lot about your personality. See, it
才不是呢。你的星座能告诉你很多关于你性格的事情。你看，
says that an Aries is energetic and loves to socialize.
上面说白羊座精力充沛，喜欢社交。
Well you certainly match those criteria, but they're so broad they could apply to anyone.
嗯，你确实符合这些特征，但它们太宽泛了，几乎适用于任何人。
What does it say about me?
那上面说我什么？
A Capricorn is serious minded and practical. She likes to do things in conventional ways.
摩羯座严肃认真、务实。她喜欢用传统的方式做事。
That sounds just like you!
这听起来就像你！
Alright we're back. So a very interesting dialogue between these two girls talking about
好了，我们回来了。所以这两个女孩之间有一段非常有趣的对话，一个
one of them believing in the horoscope and the other one doesn't. But they mentioned
相信星座运势，另一个不信。但她们提到了
a lot of interesting things, so we're going to have two language takeaways today. Let's
很多有趣的事情，所以今天我们有两个语言要点。让我们
start with language takeaway part one.
从语言要点第一部分开始。
Language takeaway
语言要点
Alright, so one of the most common things you'll hear when we talk about the horoscope
好的，当我们谈论星座运势时，你会听到的最常见的事情之一
in English is an outlook. And an outlook can be positive or negative. So what exactly is
在英语中，outlook 是一种看法。这种看法可以是积极的，也可以是消极的。那么，到底什么是
an outlook?
一个展望？
Well, if you notice Lydia said, my outlook is very positive. So basically she's talking
嗯，如果你注意到莉迪亚说，我的 outlook 非常积极。所以她基本上是在说
about her future.
关于她的未来。
Alright, so the way that she sees the future or the way that the horoscope talks about
好的，所以她看待未来的方式，或者说星座运势所谈论的方式
the future is a positive one. So you could say, you know those eight balls? They're black
未来是积极的。所以你可以说，你知道那些八号球吗？它们是黑色的。
and they have like a message and you shake it and it gives you a message.
而且它们上面还有类似签语，你摇一摇它，就会出来一条签语。
You ask a question I think sometimes.
你问了一个问题，我有时候也会想。
You ask a question and it says outlook positive.
你问一个问题，它显示“前景乐观”。
That's right.
没错。
Outlook negative. So that means in your near future things will either be positive or negative.
前景不太乐观。所以这意味着在不久的将来，事情要么会变好，要么会变坏。
So I guess you can apply it for example to a company. You say that a company has a positive
所以我想你可以把它应用到比如一家公司上。你说一家公司有积极的一面。
outlook.
outlook. 观点。
Or even a person. You know he's a very positive person so he has a positive outlook. He thinks
甚至是一个人。你知道他是个非常积极的人，所以他有积极的心态。他认为
good things are going to happen.
好事就要来了。
Okay, very good. So talking about horoscopes, obviously we must mention the 12 zodiac signs.
好的，非常好。说到星座，我们当然要提到十二星座。
Okay, so each month has its own sign and they're not exactly the months. They're a little bit
好的，每个月都有对应的星座，而且并不完全和月份对应，会有点偏差。
different but each sign is kind of an animal or a symbol.
不同，但每个星座都是一种动物或符号。
That's right.
没错。
So for example, a lot of August is part of the Leo sign in English. That's the lion.
例如，在英语中，八月的大部分时间属于狮子座。狮子座就是狮子。
And so the lion is the animal, the zodiac.
所以狮子是动物，也是星座。
So the zodiac sign is one of these signs. Like Leo is one of the zodiac signs. And I
所以星座就是这些标志之一。比如狮子座就是其中一个星座。而我
guess all 12 signs are considered the zodiac or the horoscope.
猜所有12个星座都被认为是黄道十二宫或星象。
Exactly and you can actually talk about the zodiac in terms of other cultures. There is
没错，你其实可以从其他文化的角度来谈论黄道十二宫。有
a Chinese zodiac. So we could say it's the year of the horse. But that's a little bit
中国生肖。所以我们可以说今年是马年。但这和我们这里讨论的
different from what we're talking about here with the Western horoscope.
西方星象有点不同。
Okay, very good. So all of this actually comes down to the, as we say, the pseudoscience
好的，非常好。所以这一切实际上都归结于我们所说的伪科学
or the branch called astrology.
或称为占星学的分支。
Astrology. So this is a very hard word for some people to remember because they want
占星学。这个词对一些人来说很难记住，因为他们想
to say astronomy. But it's different. Astronomy is the scientific study of the skies, the
说天文学。但这是不同的。天文学是对天空、星星、行星等
stars, planets, things like that. Astrology is different. It's what we're talking about
的科学研究。占星学则不同。它就是我们这里讨论的
here, the horoscope and reading the stars to understand what our personal futures will
星象和通过解读星星来了解我们个人未来的
hold for us.
命运。
That's right. So astronomy is an exact science part of, I guess, physics where you talk about
没错。所以天文学是一门精确科学，属于物理学的一部分，讨论的是
the stars or the composition of the stars and their movements. Whereas in astrology
星星或星星的组成及其运动。而在占星学中，
we're talking about zodiacs and horoscopes and basically what star was in the sky when
我们讨论的是黄道十二宫和星象，基本上是你出生时天空中的星星，
you were born but in a different way. It's not very scientific.
但方式不同。它不太科学。
That's right. So astrology is normally what you would see in the newspaper when you're
没错。所以占星学通常是你会在报纸上看到的，当你
trying to find your horoscope, astrology or horoscope.
试图找到你的星象时，占星学或星象。
And actually every time you read the newspaper, if you look up your zodiac sign, it makes
实际上，每次你读报纸时，如果你查看你的星座，它会让
a prediction about your day or your week or maybe even sometimes the month or year.
对你的一天、一周，甚至有时一个月或一年的预测。
That's right. And so prediction is basically a guess about what will happen for you.
没错。所以预测基本上是对你未来会发生什么的猜测。
That's right. So many times you see that the horoscope will say finances are in trouble,
没错。很多时候你会看到星座运势说财务有麻烦，
be careful with how you spend your money. So they're making a prediction that in the
花钱要小心。所以他们是在预测
future maybe you're going to have money problems so you have to be careful.
未来你可能会遇到财务问题，所以要小心。
Exactly or in the dialogue you will have a passionate summer fling. This is a prediction.
没错，或者在对话中你会有一段热烈的夏日恋情。这就是一个预测。
It has not yet happened. It will happen.
它还没发生。它将会发生。
That's right. That's right. A prediction. So now talking a little bit more about the
没错。没错。一个预测。现在我们来多谈谈
zodiac signs that we saw in the dialogue, we mentioned two, Aries and Capricorn.
对话中提到的星座，我们提到了两个：白羊座和摩羯座。
So a lot of people who believe in astrology say that astrological signs are broken up.
很多相信占星术的人说星座是分组的。
They're divided into different kinds of sign. We have water signs, air signs, earth signs
它们被分成不同的类型。我们有水象星座、风象星座、土象星座
and fire signs. One of the famous fire signs is Aries, right?
和火象星座。著名的火象星座之一就是白羊座，对吧？
Aries. It's like the god of war in the Greek mythology.
白羊座。就像希腊神话中的战神。
That's right. So it's pronounced Aries. Aries.
没错。所以它读作Aries。Aries。
A-R-I-E-S. Aries. That's right.
A-R-I-E-S。Aries。没错。
And the other one is a Capricorn. Capricorn. So that's like a goat?
另一个是摩羯座。摩羯座。那就像一只山羊？
Yeah. It's kind of like a ram. A ram.
是的。有点像公羊。公羊。
So an earth sign. That's right. So there are 12. These are just
所以是土象星座。没错。总共有12个。这只是
two of them and obviously there are a lot more. I guess off the top of my head we have
其中两个，显然还有很多。我凭记忆能想到的还有
Taurus or Leo. There's also a Scorpio.
金牛座或狮子座。还有天蝎座。
Sagittarius. Sagittarius.
射手座。射手座。
Gemini. Gemini, which are like twins, twin people.
双子座。双子座，就像双胞胎，双胞胎的人。
There's Pisces. Virgo.
还有双鱼座。处女座。
And Virgo, the Virgin. And I don't know if we're missing anything.
还有处女座，处女。我不知道我们有没有漏掉什么。
I can't think now. We'll have to talk about it at the very end of today's lesson. But
我现在想不起来了。我们得在今天课程的最后再讨论。但
we actually have some interesting things to talk about in a minute here. We have to talk
我们实际上马上有一些有趣的事情要谈。我们得谈谈
about the personality characteristics that are common when you're talking about different
不同星座常见的性格特征。
zodiac signs. Okay. So before we get to that, let's listen
好的。在我们进入那部分之前，让我们再听一遍
to our dialogue again. Hey, Lydia. What are you reading?
我们的对话。嘿，莉迪亚。你在看什么？
I'm looking at my horoscope for this month. My outlook is very positive. It says that
我在看这个月的星座运势。我的前景非常乐观。上面说
I should take a vacation to someplace exotic and that I will have a passionate summer fling.
我应该去一个异国风情的地方度假，还会有一段热烈的夏日恋情。
What are you talking about? Let me see that. What are horoscopes?
你在说什么？让我看看。星座运势是什么？
It's a prediction of your month based on your zodiac sign. You have a different sign for
它是根据你的星座对你这个月的预测。根据你出生的
the month and date you were born in. I was born on April 15th, so I'm an Aries. When
月份和日期，你有一个不同的星座。我出生在4月15日，所以我是白羊座。你
were you born? January 5th.
是什么时候出生的？1月5日。
Let's see. You're a Capricorn. It says that you'll be feeling stress at work, but you
让我看看。你是摩羯座。上面说你在工作中会感到压力，但
could see new exciting developments in your love life. Looks like we'll both have interesting
你的爱情生活可能会有令人兴奋的新发展。看来我们俩的夏天都会很有趣。
summers. That's bogus. I don't feel any stress at
那是胡说。我在工作中没感到任何压力，
work and my love life is practically non-existent. This zodiac stuff is all a bunch of nonsense.
我的爱情生活几乎不存在。这些星座的东西全是胡扯。
No, it's not. Your astrology sign can tell you a lot about your personality. See? It
不，不是的。你的星座可以告诉你很多关于你性格的信息。看？
says that an Aries is energetic and loves to socialize.
上面说白羊座精力充沛，喜欢社交。
Well, you certainly match those criteria, but they're so broad they could apply to anyone.
嗯，你确实符合这些标准，但它们太宽泛了，可以适用于任何人。
What does it say about me? A Capricorn is serious-minded and practical.
关于我怎么说？摩羯座严肃认真且务实。
She likes to do things in conventional ways. That sounds just like you.
她喜欢用传统的方式做事。这听起来就像你。
Alright, we're back. So now, let's take a look at these personality traits on Language
好了，我们回来了。现在，让我们来看看这些性格特征，在语言
Takeaway Part 2.
学习第二部分。
Language Takeaway
语言学习
Alright, so one of the great words that we heard in today's dialogue was exotic. This
好的，我们在今天的对话中听到的一个好词是“异国风情的”。这
is not necessarily describing a person, but usually things or clothes or places. In this
不一定用来描述人，但通常用来描述事物、衣服或地方。在这个
instance, it was some place exotic. What's an exotic place?
例子中，它是一个异国风情的地方。什么是异国风情的地方？
It's basically a place that's very unique and I guess it's kind of not common to go
基本上是一个很独特的地方，我想是不太常去
there or to find. For example, many people talk about an exotic getaway going to the
或不太常见的地方。例如，很多人谈论去丛林度假，说它很异国风情，
jungle because it's so exotic. You have so many strange animals and plants and everything
因为那里有那么多奇怪的动物和植物，一切
is so unfamiliar.
都那么陌生。
Right, so in my mind, Tahiti is very exotic. It's full of jungle and there's also beaches
对，在我看来，塔希提岛非常异国风情。那里到处都是丛林，还有海滩，
and it's very unusual for someone who's from America because it's just so far away.
对一个来自美国的人来说很不寻常，因为它太远了。
That's right, exotic. So, someone can also have an exotic personality because maybe they're
没错，异国风情的。所以，一个人也可以有异国风情的性格，因为他们可能
a little bit strange or not strange but not so common, maybe unique.
有点奇怪，或者不奇怪但不那么常见，也许很独特。
Yeah, although exotic is usually kind of a sexy thing when you're talking about people.
是的，虽然当谈论人时，“异国风情的”通常有点性感的意思。
You know, she looks very exotic. That means she doesn't look like everybody else here.
你知道，她看起来很异国风情。意思是她看起来不像这里的其他人。
That's right. But another adjective to describe someone's personality is somebody that's very
没错。但另一个描述人性格的形容词是某人非常
energetic.
精力充沛。
All right, so energetic sounds like the word energy. That's because they're related. So,
好的，所以“精力充沛”听起来像“能量”这个词。那是因为它们相关。所以，
someone who's energetic has lots of energy. He or she likes to do a lot of things and
精力充沛的人有很多能量。他或她喜欢做很多事情，
wants to always go places. You know the energetic person at your office. They always drink coffee.
总是想去各种地方。你知道你办公室里那个精力充沛的人。他们总是喝咖啡。
Maybe they make everyone else really tired just listening to them.
也许他们光是说话就让其他人感到疲惫。
That's right. And actually, a person that's energetic usually also loves to socialize.
没错。实际上，精力充沛的人通常也喜欢社交。
That's right. So, loves to means they like to but they like it a lot, right? But to socialize
没错。所以“喜欢”意味着他们喜欢，但非常喜欢，对吧？而“社交”
means to talk to other people or to go to parties or to meet new people.
意味着和别人交谈，或者去参加派对，或者认识新朋友。
So if it's a verb, to socialize means to talk to people, to meet people, to greet people.
所以如果它是一个动词，“社交”意味着和人交谈、认识人、打招呼。
You love to have contact with other people.
你喜欢和别人接触。
So yeah, you're right. Very, very common for people who are energetic.
所以是的，你说得对。对于精力充沛的人来说，这非常非常常见。
Okay. And what about someone that's practical? What is that like?
好的。那务实的人呢？那是什么样的？
Someone who's practical does a lot of things. Maybe someone who's practical always comes
务实的人会做很多事情。也许务实的人总是
to their activities prepared. So in my car, I'm very practical. I have extra water and
为他们的活动做好准备。所以在我车里，我很务实。我有多余的水和
a spare tire. But you can also say, I'm a very practical person. I like to do things
备胎。但你也可以说，我是一个很务实的人。我喜欢做
that I can achieve as opposed to someone who always wants to do things that they can't
我能实现的事情，而不是那些总想做
really achieve.
无法实现的事情的人。
Okay. So a practical person is usually very realistic and very down to earth. Maybe someone
好的。所以务实的人通常非常现实，非常脚踏实地。也许一个
that's practical, if they're going on a trip, they'll only take what's necessary, not more
务实的人，如果去旅行，只会带必需品，不会多带。
than they need.
比他们需要的多。
Yeah, exactly. Let me give you a good example. I like to go hiking and sometimes I see women
对，没错。我给你举个好例子。我喜欢去远足，有时候我会看到一些女性
who have not made very practical decisions about the shoes they wear. So I like to wear
在鞋子选择上做了不太实际的决定。所以我喜欢穿
hiking boots. These are very practical. Wearing high heels on a mountain is not very practical.
登山靴。这些非常实用。在高山上穿高跟鞋就不太实际。
That's right. Okay. Very good. Now, we also mentioned that a Capricorn is serious minded
没错。好的，很好。现在，我们还提到摩羯座的人通常严肃认真
and conventional in many ways.
并且在很多方面比较传统。
Someone who's serious minded maybe doesn't like to have fun and go out and do things
一个严肃认真的人可能不喜欢玩乐、出去做些
that are silly. Someone who's serious minded is usually very practical, I think, and really
傻事。我觉得严肃认真的人通常非常实际，而且真的
has a goal, wants to achieve that goal. No time to be silly. No time to make jokes.
有目标，想要实现那个目标。没时间犯傻，没时间开玩笑。
So it doesn't necessarily mean that the person is boring, but they're just very, as you said,
所以这不一定意味着这个人很无聊，而是他们就像你说的，
practical.
很实际。
That's right.
没错。
And what about that a Capricorn also likes to do things in conventional ways?
那摩羯座喜欢用传统方式做事这一点呢？
All right. So conventional means doing something in a conventional way means that you're doing
好的。所以“传统”的意思是用传统方式做事，就是说你
it in a traditional way. So this is a thing we've always done. We've always done it in
用传统的方式来做。这是我们一直以来的做法。我们一直用
this way, and I'm going to continue to do it in this way. So the opposite is unconventional.
这种方式做，而且我会继续这样做。所以反义词是“非传统”。
That means doing things in new ways, doing things with your imagination. And so something
这意味着用新方式做事，用想象力做事。所以
that's very conventional is something that has been established, and we're just going
非常传统的事情是已经确立的，我们只是
to continue doing it that way.
继续那样做。
So for example, someone that gets married in a church is the conventional way, but someone
比如，有人在教堂结婚是传统方式，但有人
that gets married while skydiving is very unconventional.
在跳伞时结婚就非常非传统。
That's right. Unconventional. Absolutely.
没错。非传统。绝对是的。
Very good. So a lot of great vocab here. Why don't we listen to her dialogue one last time,
很好。这里有很多好词汇。我们最后再听一遍对话，
and we'll be back to talk with you a little bit more.
然后回来再跟你们聊一聊。
Hey, Lydia, what are you reading?
嘿，莉迪亚，你在看什么？
I'm looking at my horoscope for this month. My outlook is very positive. It says that
我在看这个月的星座运势。我的前景非常乐观。上面说
I should take a vacation to someplace exotic and that I will have a passionate summer fling.
我应该去一个异国风情的地方度假，还会有一段热烈的夏日恋情。
What are you talking about? Let me see that. What are horoscopes?
你在说什么？让我看看。星座运势是什么？
It's a prediction of your month based on your zodiac sign. You have a different sign for
它是根据你的星座对你这个月的预测。根据你出生的
the month and date you were born in. I was born on April 15, so I'm an Aries. When were
月份和日期，你有不同的星座。我出生在4月15日，所以我是白羊座。你是什么时候
you born?
出生的？
January 5.
1月5日。
Let's see. You're a Capricorn. It says that you'll be feeling stress at work, but you
让我看看。你是摩羯座。上面说你在工作中会感到压力，但
could see new exciting developments in your love life. Looks like we'll both have interesting
你的爱情生活可能会有令人兴奋的新进展。看来我们俩都会有个有趣的
summers.
夏天。
That's bogus. I don't feel any stress at work, and my love life is practically non-existent.
那是胡扯。我在工作中没感到任何压力，我的爱情生活几乎不存在。
This zodiac stuff is all a bunch of nonsense.
这些星座的东西全是一堆废话。
No it's not. Your astrology sign can tell you a lot about your personality. See, it
不是的。你的星座可以告诉你很多关于你性格的信息。你看，
says that an Aries is energetic and loves to socialize.
上面说白羊座精力充沛，喜欢社交。
Well, you certainly match those criteria, but they're so broad they could apply to anyone.
嗯，你确实符合这些标准，但它们太宽泛了，可以适用于任何人。
What does it say about me?
那关于我的怎么说？
A Capricorn is serious-minded and practical. She likes to do things in conventional ways.
摩羯座严肃认真、实际。她喜欢用传统方式做事。
That sounds just like you!
这听起来就像你！
Alright, so talk about the horoscopes. Which sign are you?
好的，那聊聊星座运势。你是什么星座？
I'm a Leo, which is actually... I don't believe in the horoscope, but I have to say, every
我是狮子座，其实……我不相信星座运势，但我得说，每次
time someone tells me about Leos, Leo the Lion, right? I agree with most of their descriptions
有人跟我讲狮子座，狮子王，对吧？我同意他们对我性格的大部分描述。
of my personality. So, outspoken, loves to socialize, very opinionated, which means I
比如，直言不讳、喜欢社交、很有主见，这意味着我
have an opinion and I don't like to listen to other people, loves to argue very loud.
有自己的观点，不喜欢听别人的，喜欢大声争论。
So these are all qualities that I think I have, and some of them are bad, some of them
所以这些都是我觉得自己有的特质，有些是坏的，有些
are good, but you know, that's the way it is.
是好的，但你知道，就是这样。
But you don't really believe in what magazines or newspapers say about your outlook?
但你真的不相信杂志或报纸上说的关于你前景的话吗？
Nah, I don't... yeah, the predictions are usually just basic guesses. But what about
不，我不……嗯，那些预测通常只是基本的猜测。但
you? What's your sign?
你呢？你是什么星座？
I am a Taurus, so I was born in May.
我是金牛座，所以我出生在五月。
A bull.
一头牛。
A bull, yes. So I'm very stubborn and very strong. I don't really know what all the characteristics
一头牛，是的。所以我非常固执，非常强壮。我不太清楚金牛座的所有
about the Taurus are.
特征。
Opinionated?
有主见？
Opinionated, I know that it's stubborn.
有主见，我知道它固执。
Loves to argue?
喜欢争论？
Yeah, exactly.
对，没错。
Doesn't like to be corrected?
不喜欢被纠正？
Are you describing Taurus or are you describing me?
你是在描述金牛座还是在描述我？
Both.
两者都是。
All right, so it's actually very interesting. I think in many ways, sometimes the glove
好的，所以这其实很有趣。我觉得在很多方面，有时候
does fit and someone's zodiac sign describes them very well. But again, maybe like the
手套确实合适，一个人的星座很好地描述了他们。但同样，也许就像
dialogue says, they are very broad descriptions that basically any person can relate to.
对话里说的，这些描述非常宽泛，基本上任何人都能对号入座。
Absolutely. I think that that's one of the tricks to horoscopes or to predicting someone's
绝对是的。我认为这是星座运势或预测某人未来的
future. You tell them enough very vague things that maybe some of them will fit and some
技巧之一。你告诉他们足够多模糊的事情，也许有些会符合，有些
of them won't.
不会。
That's right.
没错。
But I'm very curious to hear about you guys. What are your signs? What's your sign? That
但我很好奇想听听你们。你们是什么星座？你的星座是什么？那
means what's your zodiac sign?
就是问你的星座是什么。
That's right. That's actually also a very common date question people say, oh, what's
没错。这其实也是一个很常见的搭讪问题，人们会说，哦，你
your sign?
是什么星座？
Or a pickup line.
或者一个搭讪语。
Hey baby, what's your sign?
嘿，宝贝，你是什么星座？
To see if you're compatible, right?
看看你们合不合，对吧？
Right. So let us know. We're not trying to pick you up. We're just curious. You'll find
对。所以告诉我们吧。我们不是想搭讪你。我们只是好奇。你会找到
a lot of the words for the zodiac in today's lesson on our website, EnglishPod.com.
今天课程中关于星座的很多词汇都在我们的网站EnglishPod.com上。
All right. We'll see you guys there.
好了，我们到时候见。
Bye.
再见。
Do it again, do it again.
再来一次，再来一次。